Preliminary Guide to the John C. Lilly papers M0786
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 6. Dolphin Repeated Word experiments
  - Test #17
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. G.E. Urbanek, Ph.D. (111167-3) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. George Maling, Ph.D. (111167-4) (orig) (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (1 of 6 Subj.) Test #17 Stim: "Trapped" 111167 Subj. George Maling, Ph.D. (111167-4) (copy) (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Test #18
    - Test #18 Master List of Subjects (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 171167 Subj: 171167 (orig) (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 171167 Subj: 171167 (copy) (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 181167 Subj: 181167 (orig) (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 181167 Subj: 181167 (copy) (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (V.A. Hosp) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 241167(B) Subj. 091067 & 241167-1 thru -62 (orig) (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Topeka, Kan) Test #18 Stim. "Cogitate" 221167 Subj. 091067 (copy) (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Topeka, Kan) Test #18 Stim. "Cogitate" 221167 Subj. 091067 (orig) (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Topeka, Kan) Test #18 Stim. "Cogitate" 221167 Subj. 221167 (orig) (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Topeka, Kan) Test #18 Stim. "Cogitate" 221167 Subj. 221167 (copy) (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (V.A. Hosp) Test #18 Stim. "Cogitate" 241167(A) Subj: 091067 & 241167-1 thru-62 (orig) (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (V.A. Hosp) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 241167(A) Subj.091067 & 241167-1 thru-62 (copy) (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Topeka, Kan) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 261167 Subj. 091067 (orig) (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (V.A. Hosp) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 241167(B) Subj. 091067 & 241167-1 thru-62 (copy) (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Topeka, Kan) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 261167 Subj. 091067 (copy) (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Topeka, Kan) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 261167 Subj. 261167-1 (copy) (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Topeka, Kan) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 261167 Subj: 261167-1 (orig) (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Topeka, Kan) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 261167 Subj: 261167-2 (orig) (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Topeka, Kan) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 261167 Subj. 261167-2 (copy) (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 281167 Subj. Mrs. Helen Bonny (281167) (orig) (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 281167 Subj. Mrs. Helen Bonny (281167) (copy) (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Tors home-Cal) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 011267 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (orig) (1 of 5 subjects) (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Tors home-Cal) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 011267 Subj. J.C. Lilly (091067) (copy) (1 of 5 subjects) (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Tors home-Cal) Test #18 Stim "Cogitate" 011267 Subj. Mrs. Jeniager (011267-1) (orig) (1 of 5 subjects) (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Tors home-Cal) Test #18 STim: "Cogitate" 011267 Subj. Mrs. Jeniager (011267-2) (copy) (1 of 5 subjects) (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Tor's home-Cal) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 011267 Subj. Mrs. Ivan Tors (011267-2) (orig) (1 of 5 subjects) (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Tor's home-Cal) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 011267 Sub. mrs. Ivan Tors (011267-2) (copy) (1 of 5 subjects) (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Tor's home-Cal) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 011267 Subj. Ivan Tors (011267-3) (orig) (1 of 5 subjects) (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Tor's home-Cal) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 011267 Subj. Ivan Tors (011267-3) (copy) (1 of 5 subjects) (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Tor's home-Cal) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 011267 Subj. Oscar Jeniager, M.D. (011267-4) (orig) (1 of 5 subjects) (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Tors home-Cal) Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" 011267 Subj. Oscar Jeniager, M.D. (011267-4) (copy) (1 of 5 subjects) (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #18 Stim "Cogitate" Table IV (orig) (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #18 Stim "Cogitate" Table IV (Original for Kopy Kat) (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #18 Stim. "Cogitate" Table IV (3 M Copies) (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Rm. 41) Test #18: Stim "Cogitate" 120668 Subj. 120668 (orig) (Box 26, Folder 74)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Rm. 41) Test #18 Stim "Cogitate" 120668 Subj. 120668 (copy) (Box 26, Folder 75)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. 171167-131267 Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. 171167-131267 Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate" (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #18 Stim: "Cogitate", 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Test #19
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #19 Stim "Let's go out there" Tor's home (Calif) (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Test #20
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" Table V (orig) (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 21167 Subj. 101067 (orig) (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 211267 Subj. 101067 (copy) (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 131267 Subj. H.M.T. (101867) Lieberman (131267) (orig) (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020368A Subj. 020368 (1 of 3) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020368B Subj. 020368 (1 of 3) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020368A Subj. 091067 (2 of 3) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020368B Subj. 091067 (2 of 3) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim. "Cogitate" 020368A Subj. 091067A (3 of 3) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 02036B Subj. 091067A (3 of 3) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test # "Cogitate" 020368 RVOO Orcina Orca (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 131267 Subj. H.M.T. (101867) Lieberman (131267) (copy) (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268A Subj. 220268-1 (1 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268B Subj. 220268-1 (1 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268B Subj. 220268-2 (2 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268A Subj. 220268-3 (3 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268A Subj. 220268-2 (2 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268B Subj. 220268-3 (3 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268A Subj. 220268-4 (4 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim. "Cogitate" 220268B Subj. 220268-4 (4 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268A Subj. 220268-5 (5 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268B Subj. 220268-5 (5 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268A Subj. 220268-6 (6 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268B Subj. 220268-6 (6 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268A Subj. 220268-7 (7 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268B Subj. 220268-7 (7 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268A Subj. 220268-8 (8 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268B Subj. 220268-7 (8 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268B Subj. 091067 (9 of 9) (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" 220268A Subj 091067 (9 of 9) (O&C) (Box 26, Folder 53)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568A (orig) (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568A (copy) (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568B (orig) (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568B (copy) (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568-1A (orig) (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568-1A (copy) (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568-1B (orig) (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568-1B (copy) (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568-2A (orig) (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568-2A (copy) (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568-2B (orig) (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim "Cogitate" 020568-2B (copy) (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Stanford Univ) Test #20 Stim: Cogitate 050768 B, 9 subjects (copies) (Box 26, Folder 66)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Stanford Univ) Test #20 Stim: Cogitate 050768 A, 9 subjects (copies) (Box 26, Folder 67)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" Table V Original copy (Box 26, Folder 73)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. (Stanford Univ) Test #20 Stim: Cogitate 050768 A & B, 9 subjects (originals) (Box 26, Folder 76)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" Table V (3M copies) (Box 26, Folder 77)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate" Table V Orig for Kopy Kat (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20 Stim: "Cogitate", 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #20, master subject list, 1967-1968 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Test #27
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #27 Stim: "Automatically" Subj: Fernando E. Lee (020168) (copy) (Box 26, Folder 68)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #27 Stim: "Automatically" Subj. Fernando E. Lee (020168) (orig) (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Test #28
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #28 Stim: "Tursiops" 010168 Subj. 040168-1-2-3-4(Gregory family) (orig) (Box 26, Folder 71)
    - Repeated Word-Sent. Exp. Test #28 Stim: "Tursips" 040168 Subj. 040168-1-2-3-4 (Gregory family) (copy) (Box 26, Folder 72)
- Series 7. Non-dolphin articles, papers, reports, etc.
  - Facial Expressions (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Bibliographies (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - LSD Reward and Punishment (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Ms.: Preliminary Development of a Theory of the Operations of the Mind & the Brain: The Human Computer by JCL - onf. Sci. Philos. & Relig. 070366 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Cover for: A Theory of the Operations of the Mind and Brain: The Human Being as a Computer? with observations by JCL (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - JCL Notes - Human Computer (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Notes on Theories of Communication J.C. Lilly 18 May 1963 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Extraterrestrial Intelligent Life Conf. National Radio Astronomy Observatory Nov 1-2 1961 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Notes on Organization of Teaching Program for Med. Students (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Communication - A Basic Determinant of Intellect. J.C. Lilly 20 June 1961. Scientific Seminar. Off. Secy. of Defense (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Education for Insight, Responsibility and Self-Discipline. J.C.L. 31 July 1966 1s Unit. Ch., Miami (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Prospects in the Search for Extraterrestrial Civilizations F.D. Drake (Notes by J.C.L.) (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - The Human Computer: Application of Computer Theory to the Human Mind. J.C.L. Jan 19, 1966 Lecture (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Ms.: Interacerebral Reward & Punishment: Implications for Psycho-Pharmacology by JCL 081266 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Biochemistry & Behavior, van Nostrand (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Human Biocomputer (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Programming and Metaprogramming in the Human Biocomputer (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Bibliography (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Continuous Text Data for Master Tape: Creation of "Noise" Out of Intelligible Speech (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Advertisement - Boron (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Current Biography John C. Lilly Nov. 1962, Vol. 23, No 10 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Truby, Henry M. Bibliography 1940-1967 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - "Sciences" vs Science March 1958 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Motivation Control with Electrical Brain Stimulation of Non-Human Species: Communication with Individuals and Use as Agents (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Robert S. Morrison Letters about Reciprocity Proposal (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Electronic Integrator (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Ideas: Gadgetry 1946 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Metals: electrochemical, corrosion (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Metals: Hg + W emission spectra (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Multiple Function Analyzer (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Photoconductive Cells (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Tape Recorder: Specs for 18 Channel Electro-Physiology (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report of the Basic Research Program, NIMH-NINDB (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - NIH Official Reports (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Brain Stimulation Electrodes (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Start-Stop Systems (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - General Research Brain Stimulation (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - USPHS Grant #B32 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Ultramicrometer Circuit June 1943 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Injury & Excitation of Brain by Electrical Currents J.C. Lilly NIH, Bethesda, Md. (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Electrical Stimulation of the Brain: Theory (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Electrical Injury to Brain Theory (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - The Brain Stimulator (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Deep Electro-Therapy Committee (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - JCL Annual Progress Report NB-03097-06 rough draft (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Final draft - 1967 Director's Report to the board (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Rough draft of Director's Report to Board June Meeting 1967 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Budget 1967-68 Extra copies of the budget included in the Proposal for the 256 Channel (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - JCL Annual Progress REport NB-03097-06 original (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Robert White CV (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - 256 Channel Device
    - 256 Channel device NSF (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - AF-AFS04-415-66 Annual Report (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Proposal for 256 Channel device (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Proposal (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Proposal for Development of a 256 Channel Device for Pickup, Recording, Storing, and Reproducing Electrical Signals Distributed in Space. AFOSR - 15 June 1967 JCL Rough Drafts (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Proposal for Development of a 256 Channel Device for Pickup, Recording, Storing, and Reproducing Electrical Signals Distributed in Space. AFOSR 15 June 1967 JCL 1st Copy (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Proposal for Development of a 256 Channel Device for Pickup, Recording, Storing, and Reproducing Electrical Signals Distributed in Space. AFOSR 15 June 1967 JCL Reprints (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Proposal for Development of a 256 Channel Device for Pickup, Recording, Storing, and Reproducing Electrical Signals Distributed in Space. AFOSR 15 June 1967 JCL Original Copy (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - 256 Channel Device for Pickup (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Misc No Author + Multiple Authors (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Misc No Author + Multiple Authors (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Negatives Monkey 110956 slide (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - 4th Neuropharmacology Sept. 25-27, 1957 J.C. Lilly (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Intracerebral Reward and Punishment
    - Intracerebral Reward and Punishment: Implications for Psychopharmacology (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Intracerebral Reward and Punishment: Implications for Psychopharmacology - Final Copy of Manuscript (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Intracerebral Reward and Punishment: Implications for Psychopharmacology Galleyproof (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Intracerebral Reward and Punishment: Implications for Psychopharmacology Figures (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Intracerebral Reward and Punishment: Implications for Psychopharmacology Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - MS: Proposal for Research Program on the Relations Between the Activities of the Brain Body and Mind: May 1952 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Series 8. Dolphin & non-dolphin articles, papers, reports, notes, correspondence, workshops
  - Lilly, Simulations of God: The Science of Belief [inscribed copy] (Box 154, Object 10)
  - Magical Blend Issue 36 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - JCL Programming & Metaprogramming, Esalen Institute, February 74 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Self-Programs & Metaprograms Book III 1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Human Biocomputer & Beyond MS, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Rep-Rap & Map (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Notes to Be Typed (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Po (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Lecture 1/19/74 - The Holograms & Language of All (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Tank Design, Use, & S.I.C. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Notes Already Typed (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Photos # 1-21 Sent to Crown, NYC 5 May 1978 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Text Figures (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Glossy Prints (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Text Figures 10-13, Plates 22-A, 25-A, 37-A, 42-44 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Communication Between Man & Dolphin, 20 June 1978 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Plates 45-47, Scientific Investigations CRI 1964 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Plates 22-30, 34, 35, 41 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Acoustic Space & Objects (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Visible Speech, Bell Telephone System (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Future Detectors in the Perception of Speech (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Multi-Channel Design (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Cortical Folding & Cortical Surface (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Communication with Extraterrestrial Intelligence (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Vol. III (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - The Science of Yoga (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - The Gross Anatomy and Fine Structure of the Auditory Apparatus, Bloome 1968 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Porpoise, Dolphin & Small Whale Fisheries of the World (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Catalogo de los Mamiferos Vivientes Y Extinguidos de las Antillas (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Los Angeles Times, July 10 1994 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Optical Electronics, Inc (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - HDF Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Summary Manuscript 5 Feb 1974 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Phon Study 27 April 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Paper on Cogitate Results (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - The Human Biocomputer: Theory, Belief & Hypothesis (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Speech References (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Practice Programs on SR-52 and Printer PC100 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Eigen Values 9 March 1977 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Science 26 Sept. 1980, 24 Oct. 1980 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Toni Lilly Notebook (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Report on Work at St. Thomas July 1963-September 1964 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - An Atlas of the Brain of the Dolphin (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Notebook 1978 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - RCA Video Equipment (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - BJC Computer - instructions, working file (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Barbara Cuark (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Saul-Paul Sirag (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - HDF Misc (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Robert F. Edwards May 31, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Robert F. Edwards May 20, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Conversations with Spanky, A Killer Whale (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Molly (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - New Memberships & Current Orders (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Sonagraph & Related Equipment (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Chimpanzee Conversations (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Introduction to HDF (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - The Personal Survival Game 1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - The Quandary of Whether to Retain or Release Rehabilitated Strandlings (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Subliminal Communication & Hypnosis (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Dissimilarities Between Lucid Dream and Waking Cognition (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Human/Computer Relationships 1983 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Misc Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Ring, Prof. Kenneth (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Ridgway, Sam H. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Hardware files
    - Hardware: Color Terminals, technical data (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Hardware: Displays (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Hardware: Terminals (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Hardware: Termiflex Corp. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Hardware: Telemetry (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Hardware: Voltage Protection (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Hardware: Unibus Micro-Computers (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Hardware: Voice Peripherals (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Hardware: Voice Recognition (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Hardware: Logic Probe (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Hardware: Other Transducers (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Hardware: Rental Equipment (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Hardware: Keithley Instruments (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Hardware: Hydrophones - B&K (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Hardware: Voice Synthesis (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Hardware: A/D Converters - Analogic (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Software
    - Software: DECUS (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Software: Dr. Dobbs (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Software: Ezedit (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Software: Fourth Language (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Software: Miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Software: Pascal (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Software: Computer Music (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Project Interlock (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Project OPRA (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - The Pygmy Fund (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Potentials: B. Max-Hubbard (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Quotes: Aristotle (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Q Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Ram Dass/Feynman (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Esalen Workshop: "Energy Awareness & Love" (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Workshop at Samadhi Tank Company for Human/Dolphin Foundation (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Forest Farms Samadhi Workshop: November, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - M.D. workshop (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - M.D.S. workshop (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Series 9. Reprints, by author [M-Z incomplete]
  - McVay, Scott (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Maier, Richard A. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - McCormick, James G. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - McCormick, James G., et al (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - McFarland, W.L. et al (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Norris, Ken S. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Morozov, V.P. and Akopian, A.I. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - McFarland, William N. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - McFarland, W.L. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Nagel, E.C. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Morgane, Peter (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Mohl, B. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Maier, R.A. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Moris, Francois (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Nagel, E.L. et al (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Northrop, J. et al (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Norris, Kenneth S. and G.W. Harvey (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Morozov, V.P. and A.I. Akopian et al (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Navy Publications (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Norris, Kenneth S. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Norris, K.S. (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Morozov, V.P. (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Pilleri, G., C. Kraus, and M. Gihr (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Pilleri G. and M. Gihr (Box 32, Folder 24)